Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - Carrie Kuehl needs a ride and walking companion for tomorrow's rally on Sanctuary for immigrants and refugees at the State Capitol., 2017 February 6
    - Tuesday, February 7th event at Hamilton Union Presbyterian Church, Guilderland NY "Love Stories", 2017 February 6
    - The Islamic Center of the Capital District opening a Food Pantry - Your support is needed, 2017 February 6
    - Reminder: Women Against War Annual Gathering This Feb 8th - Speaker Phyllis Bennis, Awardee Trudy Quaif Please RSVP, 2017 February 6
    - Petition against prison visit cutbacks, 2017 February 6
    - Join a national call on Feb. 9th about the #MoralMarch, 2017 February 7
    - ACTION: THIS THURSDAY, February 9th, 5pm - Prot Congressman Faso at Fort Orange Club, ALSO CALL ASAP to SUPPORT NYC's bag ban and Albany County's Styrofoam ban, 2017 February 7
    - Sunday, February 12th at 4 PM, Important Intersectional Event in Saratoga "Uniting Communities Against the Politics of Hate", 2017 February 8
    - Donations to the new food pantry at ICC. The Islamic Center of the Capital District is starting a Food Pantry - Your support is needed., 2017 February 8
    - Grannies for Peace Annual Valentine's Vigil Tuesday, February 14, 2017, Noon to 1 PM, Wolf Road and Central Avenue, near Colonie Shopping Center. "Spread Love Not Hate!", 2017 February 9
    - Fwd: Save the date NATIONAL CLIMATE MARCH, 2017 February 9
    - coffee hour postponed, 2017 February 12
    - The Rise of American Authoritarianism, 2017 February 13
    - Three important and upcomimg events: rescheduled from snowstorm, or scheduled soon. Sunday, 2/19, Monday 2/20, Wednesday, 2/22, 2017 February 15
    - 4 Vusi and All Stars CONCERT as new season looms, Friday, February 17th at The Egg. Fundraiser for WOOC 105.3 FM, 2017 February 16
    - Wonderful article about Trudy Quaif, Our Woman of Peace awardee, 2017 February 16
    - Tuesday, February 21, 7:00 p m, BNP General Membership Mee ting "How can we Stop the Trump Agenda?" Bethlehem Town Hall, 2017 February 17
    - Please Make a comment about the Dakota Access Pipeline to the Army Corps of Engineers: Deadline Feb. 20th And 2 chances to see free film about Standing Rock, 2/18, Saratoga and 2/27, Albany., 2017 February 17
    - New blog article about Energetic Valentine's Day Vigil with excellent photos, story poem by Dan Wilcox, description of great refugee support scholarship fund at Albany HS., 2017 February 17
    - AP breaking news...100,000 National Guards to do what? Petition and alert., 2017 February 18
    - Say No to Trump Troops Against Immigrants. More about the draft plan and a petition against it., 2017 February 19
    - February 25 symposium, "Advocacy and Activism Under the Trump Administration", all day, Albany Law School, 2017 February 19
    - Forum on Immigration Sunday, February 26 2-4 PM, St. Sophia Church, Albany, 2017 February 19
    - Topics of Panels at February 25 symposium, "Advocacy and ActivismUnder the Trump Administration", all day, Albany Law School, 2017 February 20
    - New Event! Tues. 2/21, Sacco & Vanzetti Brown Bag Lunch, 12:15 PM Husted Hall, Downtown Campus -- and Friday, 2/24, Page Hall, 7 PM, 2017 February 20
    - Fwd: [Roundtable] A COMMUNITY CONVERSATION ON IMMIGRATION IN THE CAPITAL DISTRICT - LEAGUE OF WOMEN VOTERS EVENT - SUNDAY, FEBRUARY 26, 2-4 PM, ST. SOPHIA'S CHURCH, 2017 February 21
    - Fwd: Women's March Resistance Voter Registration !, 2017 February 22
    - Not To Miss!! Salif Keita at the Sanctuary for Independent Media, Sunday, April 2, 2017. 7 PM -10 PM. Reserved, advance ordered tickets, 2017 February 23
    - 15 Seconds of Activism to count against Steve Bannon on the NSC. Quick phone call to Senate Committee on Homeland Security., 2017 February 23
    - ACTION ALERT: RALLY ON MARCH 31 AT 3 PM TO SUPPORT FUNDING FOR REFUGEE LEGAL AND RESETTLEMENT SERVICES!, 2017 February 24
    - RE: ACTION ALERT: RALLY ON MARCH 1 AT 3 PM TO SUPPORT FUNDING FOR REFUGEE LEGAL AND RESETTLEMENT SERVICES!, 2017 February 24
    - SAVE THE DATE:March 23rd Capital Rep AN ILIAD, with special TALK BACK led by SOLDIER's HEART: Ed Tick and Kate Dahladt and WAW POSTER EXHIBIT "HUMANIZE NOT MILITARIZE", 2017 February 26
    - Reminder: Free screening tonight of Standing Rock Film 7 to 8:30 pm - TONIGHT: MONDAY 2/27, Hubbard Interfaith Sanctuary, College of St. Rose, 2017 February 27
    - Report Back from Tom Ellis about his Paline/Israel Trip. Wednesday, March 1st 7 PM to 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library, Delmar NY, 2017 February 27
    - FW: event next Saturday re: Trump's executive order on immigrants, 2017 February 27
    - People"s March for Free Press and buses to several other marches in March, April and May, 2017 February 28
    - RE: REMINDER - ACTION ALERT: RALLY ON MARCH 1 AT 3 PM TO SUPPORT FUNDING FOR REFUGEE LEGAL AND RESETTLEMENT SERVICES!, 2017 February 28
    - URGENT: Immigrant Defense Needed, Wednesday, March 1st, 8:20 am, USCIS office, 1086 Troy Schenectady Road to stop a deportation., 2017 March 1
    - REMINDER: RALLY TOMORROW, WEDNESDAY, MARCH 1 AT 3 PM TO SUPPORT FUNDING FOR REFUGEE LEGAL AND RESETTLEMENT SERVICES!, 2017 March 1
    - Reminder: Celebrate Women's History Month with Local Trailblazers and a play "Petticoats of Steel" Thursday, March 2nd, 5:30 PM, Huxley Theater in NY State Museum, 2017 March 1
    - People's March for Education Justice, Saturday, March 4th Noon, North Brandywine Avenue and State Street, Schenectady, starting point of the march, 2017 March 1
    - Poster with all of the Capital District Dates of Humanize Not Militarize Poster Exhibit and details about the first exhibit at Capital Repertory from March 10th through April 2nd and a special "Talk Back" event on March 23rd., 2017 March 2
    - Professor Keeanga Yamahtta Taylor, Tuesday, March 7th, 4:00 PM, Albany Law School, Reception to follow. PLEASE RSVP, 2017 March 2
    - [upstatedroneaction] Press Release: ACQUITTED! 4 Drone Resisters from Big Books Action @ Hancock Airbase, 2017 March 3
    - Barbara Smith's article:"WHY WE ARE STRIKING ON MARCH 8th." Rally on Wednesday, March 8th, Townsend Park, Albany, 11:30 am -1:30 PM, 2017 March 3
    - Rally on Wednesday, March 8th, Townsend Park, Albany, 11:30 am -1:30 PM New Flyer for the local march attached and more., 2017 March 4
    - Update on SPECIAL TICKET PRICE AND PURCHASE FOR MARCH 23rd AN ILIAD PERFORMANCE, 2017 March 5
    - Please let women friends know!--Thanks! A Gathering for Women, Saturday, March 18, 2017, 1 PM to 4:30 PM W Hill Branch, 148 Henry Johnson Blvd, Albany, 2017 March 6
    - Press Release for March 23 Program in Pittsfield, "Why Fors Matter" 7 to 8:45 PM, Berkshire Athenaeum Public Library, Pittsfield MA, 2017 March 6
    - Immigrant defense/accompanimentl at USCIS on Wednesday, March 8th at 12:30 PM For mother of 5 US born children is threatened with deportation. Details below., 2017 March 7
    - Reminder:, Tomorrow, International Women's Day in Albany,, Townsend Park, 11:30 to 1:30 PM or if you can't be there then wear RED and see more suggions from WAND, 2017 March 7
    - Register Now to Beat MuslimBan 2.0. Webinar Thursday, March 9th, Noon, eastern time., 2017 March 8
    - Quick update on Standing Rock- Albany County Styrofoam Ban Vote on Monday March 13th. Buses to Peoples Climate March on Saturday April 29th, 2017 March 9
    - Tpmorrow, March 11th at 1 PM Film and Discussion 13th: From Slavery to Mass Incarceration, S C Public Library 948 State Street, Schenectady, 2017 March 10
    - "Justice Does Not Compromise" Rally Monday March 13 at NOON w capitol park Albany, 2017 March 10
    - Please Join Women Against War for special performance of AN ILIAD on Thurs, March 23rd - special ticket prices!, 2017 March 11
    - Tuesday, March 14th, 7 PM Where Healthcare is a Human Right: Cuba' s Community Doctors Film at Huyck Auditorium, Albany Medical College, 2017 March 12
    - BUSES TO PEOPLE'S CLIMATE MARCH in DC, SAT. April 29th, 2017 March 13
    - POSTPONED DUE TO STORM: Tuesday, March 1 4th, 7 PM Where Healthcare is a Human Right: Cuba's Community Doctors Film at Huyck Auditorium, Albany Medical College, 2017 March 13
    - [undergroundrailroad] Liberty Conference 2017 - Register Now to Reserve Your Space for March 24th, 25th and 26th, 2017 March 13
    - Fast for Yemen: Week long Fast and series of actions in NYC starting April 10th but people can join wherever they are., 2017 March 15
    - Albany Social Justice Center announcement, 2017 March 15
    - Remembering Rachel Corrie on the 14th anniversary o f her killing. Rachel presente! A virtual vigil., 2017 March 16
    - Remembering Rachel Corrie on the 14th anniversary of her killing. Rachel presente! A virtual vigil., 2017 March 16
    - "Is Anybody Listening?" - Screening & Discussion, Tuesday April 4th, at 7 PM, Lally Education Building, College of St. Rose, 2017 March 17
    - Monday, March 20th. 5 PM to 6 PM. BNP Vigil "End the Escalation of Wars in Iraq, Yemen and Syria - on the anniversary of the Iraq invasion, 2017 March 18
    - Albany CROP Hunger Walk, May 7th - CROP Recruiters Rally on Sunday, March 26 4:30 PM to 6:30 PM website and descriptions below., 2017 March 18
    - RE:Tuesday, March 14th, 7 PM Whe re Healthcare is a Human Right: Cuba 's Community Doctors Film at Huyc k Auditorium, Albany Medical College, 2017 March 19
    - Reminder: Special performance of anti-war play AN ILIAD this Thursday!, 2017 March 20
    - COSECHA UPSTATE NY Prxima ACCION! / / Next ACTION!, Saturday, March 25th, 5:30-7:30pm Art Street Action Lark Street and Washington Avenue, Albany, 2017 March 21
    - TODAY! TWEET for the TREES! [On International Day for Fors.] One of our previous speakers at Women Against War's annual gathering in 2013. Rachel Smolker, 2017 March 21
    - Fwd: Interfaith Art Show, 2017 March 21
    - DATE CORRECTION FROM ORIGINAL SUBJECT HEADING:C OSECHA UPSTATE NY Prxima ACCION! // Next ACTION !, FRIDAY, March 24th, 5:30-7:30pm Art Street A ction Lark Street and Washington Avenue, Albany, 2017 March 22
    - VOLUNTEERS NEEDo be trained and then help ting students in the RISSE Adult ESL program., 2017 March 23
    - Help keep visits at NYS prisons!, 2017 March 24
    - Re: WAWaction Help keep visits at NYS prisons!, 2017 March 25
    - Important Anti-Pipeline Rally this Monday 3/27 at DEC building in Albany, NOON, 2017 March 25
    - Fund Raising Party for New Sanctuary for Immigrants, Saturday, April 1st, 6 to 8:30 PM, Shrine of our Lady of the Americas, 273 Central Avenue, Albany, 2017 March 27
    - Associate Justice of the United States Supreme Court, Sonia Sotomayor, MORE Free Tickets, Tuesday, April 4th at the SEFCU Arena, 6:30 PM, 2017 March 28
    - U.S. Drone War docufilm National Bir d w/ filmmaker Sonia Kennebeck Showin g at The Sanctuary for Independent Med ia, Monday April 17th, 7 PM to 9:30 PM, 2017 March 28
    - See different Humanize Not Militarize posters at UAlbany with play, REBEL Sister, 2017 March 28
    - Film Showing: Cuba's Community Doctors, Tuesday, April 4th, 7 PM to 10 PM, Huyck Auditorium Albany Medical College 43 New Scotland Ave, Albany, NY., 2017 March 29
    - NATIONAL MUSLIM SOUP KITCHEN DAY - SATURDAY APRIL 29 - VOLUNTEERS FROM ALL FAITHS AND BACKGROUNDS NEEDED!!!, 2017 March 30
    - Defend Immigrants - Monday April 3rd, 9:30am ICE OFFICE, 1086 Troy-Schenectady Rd DETAILS BELOW, 2017 April 1
    - Health Care is a Human Right. Day of Action April 4, Lobby Day, 10 am to 3 PM, and Rally at 11:30 am Albany Legislative Building and W Capitol Park, 2017 April 2
    - COMMUNITY DOCTORS: An Inside View into Cuba's Health Care System- Tuesday April 4, 7PM- Huyck Auditorium, Albany Medical College 43 New Scotland Ave, Albany, NY, 2017 April 3
    - Talk By Larry Wittner, Thursday, April 6 th 7 to 8:45 PM,Bethlehem Public Library: "A Nuclear Arms Race,or a Nuclear-Free World?", 2017 April 3
    - Friday--Black Panthers Film w/ MacArthur Genius Stanley Nelson, Friday, April 7th, 7 PM, Page Hall, Downtown Campus, Albany, 2017 April 4
    - Docunight #36 Wednesday, April 5, 7-9 PM Draper Hall, 135 Wern Avenue, Albany "Sonita" story about an 18 year old Afghan Refugee in Tehran, 2017 April 4
    - Endangered Species? Future of Journalism: Thurs, April 20th, 6:30PM, 2017 April 4
    - From Phyllis Bennis: NEW SIGN-ON STATEMENT- Movements uniting against militarism on 50th anniversary of MLK speech "BEYOND VIETNAM", 2017 April 5
    - Reminder: Talk By Larry Wittner, TOMORROW, April 6 th 7 to 8:45 PM ,Bethlehem Public Library: "A Nuclear Arms Race,or a Nuclear-Free World?", 2017 April 5
    - Larry Wittner April 6, 2017 April 6
    - After Spring: Jon Stewart's new, critically acclaimed film on Syrian Refugees: Fri, April 14, 7 PM, FUUSA, 2017 April 6
    - FRIDAY - Runaway Inequality: How bad it is and what we can do about it - Les Leopold at James Connolly Forum, Troy, April 8, 2017 April 6
    - Good Statement from FCNL: Stop U.S. from making Syria war even worse, 2017 April 7
    - Monday, April 10 - 5:00 - 6:00 pm, BNP Vigil: "End the Escalation of War in Syria", 2017 April 8
    - JOIN INTERFAITH SOLIDARITY MARCH FOR IMMIGRANTS AND REFUGEES - APRIL 10 AT 4:30 PM STARTING AT THE FRIENDS MEETING HOUSE 727 AVENUE, 2017 April 8
    - Pastors for peace event, Friday, April 21st First Unitarian Society of Albany, 5:30 to 8:30 PM, 2017 April 10
    - Immigration Open Forum, Monday April 17 at 4:30-6PM UALBANY Campus Center Assembly Hall, 2017 April 11
    - Faso Watch during recess: Planned Parenthood Rallies April 13, 14 and 19, Various locations and times., 2017 April 11
    - Reminder: This Friday, April 14, After Spring: Jon Stewart's new, critically acclaimed film on Syrian Refugees: 7 PM, FUUSA, 2017 April 12
    - Free Hudson Valley shows on indigenous rights, social justice, and the environment. Poughkeepsie 4/19, Woodstock 4/22, 2017 April 12
    - Save the Date: Grannies for Peace Vigil at Tulip Fival on Saturday, May 13, 1 PM on Mother's Day Weekend, 2017 April 13
    - Humanize, Not Militarize Poster Exhibit Opening at Sage, Presentation by Dr. Mussarat Chaudhry & Reception, this Mon, April 17, 6 PM, 2017 April 15
    - Reminder- National Bird, Drone Whistleblower film, Monday, April 17th, Workshop from 4:30-6 PM; Community Potluck and Art Opening, 6 PM-7PM; Screening of National Bird 7PM- 9:30 PM, 2017 April 15
    - Bill McKibben, Monday April 17rh 5:30 to 6:30 PM, Nott Memorial, Union College, Schenectady, get there early, Reception at 5 PM and talk at 5:30 PM, 2017 April 16
    - Monday, April 17 - 5:00 - 6:00 pm, BNP Vigil: "Diplomacy, NOT Endless War" Four Corners, Delmar NY, 2017 April 16
    - Innovative program about Social, Political and Religious Reconciliation, WEDNESDAY, April 19rh, 1 PM to 2:30 PM, from Rockefeller Institute, Location: Linda Norris Auditorium, 339 Central Avenue, Albany, 2017 April 17
    - BNP Community Discussion, Tuesday, April 18, 7:00 -9:00 pm, Bethlehem Town Hall:, 2017 April 17
    - Reminder from the League of Women Voters: The Future of Journalism and the 1st Amendment, April 20, 6:30 - 8:30 PM, Delmar Reformed Church, 2017 April 18
    - UPDATED - ICE OFFICE ACTION - WED APRIL 19 8:30AM in support of Maria at her next appointment with ICE, 2017 April 18
    - Thursday, 4/20 Abu Ghraib interrogator Eric Fair and his crisis of conscience 8 PM Clark Auditorium, NYState Museum, Cultural Education Center, Albany, 2017 April 19
    - Earth Day March for Science - Saturday, April 22 at 1 pm at Capitol Park W. Family friendly day!, 2017 April 19
    - Film premiers from Persian-speaking communities and the greater Middle East region at Proctors, 2017 April 20
    - ANYONE INTERED IN VOLUNTEERING TO TEACH COMPUTER LITERACY TO REFUGEES AND IMMIGRANTS?, 2017 April 20
    - Shut Down Creech 2017! Mass Mobilization to Stop the Drone Wars April 23 - April 29, 2017, 2017 April 20
    - "Building the Beloved Community: Racism an d Beyond" workshops. And a play, Fires i n the Mirror. Events for the weekend start ing on Friday, April 28 - Sunday, April 30., 2017 April 21
    - Fw: April 28 and 29th flyers, 2017 April 21
    - Maria is out of her ICE appointment and updates and events from Joe Paparone of the Sanctuary City and immigrant support community., 2017 April 24
    - Reminder - Come to the Schenectady City Council TODAY at 6:30 PM To Support the message to the Schenectady City Council that they need to adopt a resolution defending all residents., 2017 April 24
    - Keep the US in the Paris Climate Agreement - and other important actions & events for Earth week!, 2017 April 24
    - (T)Error screening plus panel April 29, 2017 8 PM, Lecture Center 21, UAlbany Uptown. Film at 8 PM Panel discussion at 10 PM, 2017 April 25
    - Pot luck dinner for women supports, 2017 April 25
    - [tianys] FW: Facing the Truth: Lessons from Post-Apartheid South Africa, Wednesday, April 26 at 6 p.m. Albany Institute of Art and History., 2017 April 26
    - all Your Senators Now! Diplomacy, Not War on the Korean Peninsula Military briefing for the Senate at 3 PM this afternoon!, 2017 April 26
    - RE: WAWaction Maria is out of her ICE appointment and updates and events from Joe Paparone of the Sanctuary City and immigrant support community., 2017 April 27
    - Powerful documentary film about US drone program - on WMHT May 1 - May 8, 2017 April 27
    - May Day Interfaith March for Immigrant Rights, Monday May 1st at 11 am, Starting at the Shrine of Our Lady of the Americas 273 Central Avenue, Albany, NY. Ending at Townsend Park, 2017 April 28
    - Join 9 Senators to Tell Saudi Arabia: [The port of] "Hodeida [in Yemen] Must Be Spared"!, 2017 April 29
    - TOMORROW:, MONDAY May 1 rally and march for immigrants: Rallies at 11 am and 5 pm Albany and day long marches and workshops., 2017 April 30
    - Ride and accompaniment at interfaith march tomorrow., 2017 April 30
    - Today: Black Playwright "full of anger and compassion" Dael Orlandersmith, 4:15 PM and 8 PM, Recital Hall, Performing Arts Center., 2017 May 1
    - Viva Cinco De Mayo at Pruyn House: Saturday, May 6., 2017 May 1
    - The Capital District Coalition Against Islamophobia supports Cosecha May 1 Strike! [From the interfaith service, march and rallies on a Day Without Immigrants], 2017 May 2
    - Fw: Fwd: Cabaret for Syrian Refugees, 2017 May 2
    - Humanize Not Militarize posters at Oakwood Community Center, 5/8-20; with Soul Cafe community meal, next Mon May 8, 2017 May 4
    - Wednesday, May 10th A Day of Advocacy and Action for Parole and Prison Justice. 9:30 am Gather, 12:30 PM Rally W Capitol Park, 2017 May 8
    - Tell Ivanka: ask Dad to watch the video about imminent famine in Yemen], 2017 May 8
    - Grannies for Peace Vigil at Tulip Fival this Saturday, May 13, 1 PM on Mother's Day Weekend, 2017 May 8
    - Please join us at our annual Grannies for Peace Tulip F vigil on Saturday, May 13th in Washington Park near the Moses Statue, 1 PM to 2 PM with leafletting afterwards., 2017 May 9
    - Gathering for Women "No Limits for Women Project" Saturday, May 13th 1 to 4 PM, Arbor Hill/W Hill branch of the Albany Public Library., 2017 May 9
    - Asking for help with a project for refugee small businesses called International Peace Bazaar., 2017 May 10
    - Saturday, May 13 - Food and Water Watch The Green Energy Revolution - Citizen Action 4 PM Community video watching, 2017 May 11
    - The Future of Afghanistan Depends on Education, 2017 May 11
    - RE: WAWaction Asking for help with a project for refugee small businesses called International Peace Bazaar., 2017 May 11
    - News from the Interfaith Story Circle: Healing the Earth, Monday, May 15, 2017, 7-9 PM, Unity Church, 21 King Avenue, Albany NY, 2017 May 14
    - Invitation to join the Albany march and rally to End Endless War,Sunday, May 21, 1PM to 3 PM Townsend Park to Lafyaette Park., 2017 May 16
    - Fw: WAWaction Invitation to join the Albany march and rally to End Endless War, Sunday, May 21, 1PM to 3 PM Townsend Park to Lafyaette Park., 2017 May 16
    - How campaigns work. Recommendation to watch the video of Mat Taibbi's talk at the Sanctuary last Friday and the Q&A that follows, 2017 May 17
    - Fw: Emma's Revolution - would you help us with a last minute email?, 2017 May 18
    - #ChelseaIsFree! Now you can say this to her.. Call to communicate with Chelsea from CodePink., 2017 May 18
    - Reminder: Albany March to End Endless War, through Negotiations, Justice and Democracy, Sunday May 21st 1 PM Townsend Park, Albany., 2017 May 19
    - Interfaith statement of support for Madison family & donation info, 2017 May 19
    - Spectrum tv coverage of the End Endless War Rally yerday [Sunday, May 21st, 1 PM to 3 PM, 2017 May 22
    - More TV coverage of Sunday's event to End Endless War, at Townsend Park in Albany [Channel 13 TV interview with Joe Lombardo and more], 2017 May 23
    - Invitation to join Memorial Day Parade 2017. Veterans for Peace, step off at 9:30 AM, Monday May 29th from SE corner of Central Avenue and Partridge Street., 2017 May 23
    - NVDA training on June 17th, 10am to 4 PM, Lunch Provided, 680 Central Avenue, Albany NY 12206. Pre-Registration requed!, 2017 May 28
    - "Speed Sisters" documentary about the first all women's car racing team in Paline, Monday, June 5th, 6:30 PM, Washington Avenue branch of APL, 2017 May 29
    - Photos of the May 21st antiwar rally in a blog article with a link to Dan Wilcox's poem., 2017 May 30
    - Webinair on Refugee issues, 2017 June 3
    - POSTPONED - Immigrant Accompaniment at Latham ICE tomorrow morning. Will be rescheduled., 2017 June 4
    - Reminder: "Speed Sisters" Monday, June 5th 6:30 to 8:30 PM Washington Ave. branch of Albany Public Library, 2017 June 4
    - Joe Lombardo reports on his trip to the May 2017 NATO Meeting. Wednesday, June 7th, 7 to 9 PM, Bethlehem Public Library., 2017 June 6
    - Reproductive Health Act Petition drop off June 7 at 11:30 am. Albany Capitol 3rd floor Press Conference with supporters., 2017 June 6
    - [PAUSE] NVDA Training is filling up! Register now if you want to attend on Saturday, June 17th from 10 am to 4 PM, lunch provided., 2017 June 6
    - Webinair on Refugees now scheduled for 6/12, 2017 June 6
    - #Marking50 Vigil in Townsend Park, Albany, 7 PM, 2017 June 7
    - Activism & Art: Prot Sign Making Workshop, June 23 & AFSC Exhibit Moves to Saratoga, 2017 June 8
    - "Has the time come for Single Payer Health Care?" Tuesday, June 13th 7-9 PM, Bethlehem Town Hall, Discussion followed by Q and A., 2017 June 9
    - JUNE 15, 2017 Panel Discussion at Albany City Hall:: GETTING TO KNOW ALBANY"S REFUGEE AND IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES 5:30-7:30 PM, 2017 June 9
    - Albany County Free Speech Proclamation- TONIGHT, Monday, June 12th at 6:30PM Albany County Courthouse, 2nd floor., 2017 June 12
    - End Racism in NYS Parole System! Two events on Tuesday, June 13th Media Conference 11am, LOB - Voting Rights Day of Action rally at Noon, W Capitol Park, 2017 June 12
    - Roundtable] FW: REMINDER: JUNE 15, 2017 ROTUNDA EVENT: GETTING TO KNOW ALBANY'S REFUGEE AND IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES, 2017 June 14
    - Know Your Rights presentation at USCRI, Thursday, June 22nd 5:30 PM to 7 PM., 2017 June 15
    - UNAC conference will be live streamed Friday, June 16 through Sunday, June 18, see website for specific programming., 2017 June 16
    - Report back and analysis of May 21st rally to End Endless War, Tuesday, June 20th 7-9 PM Betnlehem Town Hall, 445 Delaware Avenue, Delmar., 2017 June 17
    - Wednesday, June 21st: Judith Enck, Former EPA Administrator, Will Speak at Save the Pine Bush Dinner about The Trump Assault on Environmental Protection, 2017 June 19